<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dotfiles on Mr Beaner - Put Coffee in your rice!</title>
    <link>///home/bud/pub/www/tags/dotfiles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dotfiles on Mr Beaner - Put Coffee in your rice!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 17:14:06 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="///home/bud/pub/www/tags/dotfiles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>compton_setup</title>
      <link>///home/bud/pub/www/blog/compton_setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 17:14:06 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>///home/bud/pub/www/blog/compton_setup/</guid>
      <description>compton is a lightweight compositor for X that works really well with i3. A compositor adds some eye-candy like transparency and drop-shadows to the windows. But it also do some anti screen tearing magic and such. The compton setup can however be a bit tricky and it all depends on your own preferences and hardware.
Below are some snippets from my .compton.conf that is more i3 then hardware related that you might find useful:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>bashrc</title>
      <link>///home/bud/pub/www/dots/bashrc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 17:21:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>///home/bud/pub/www/dots/bashrc/</guid>
      <description>Only thing going on here is a loop that sources all files in ~/.bash/ . I just upgraded Mint and it was kind enough to overwrite my .bashrc, that made me decide to have it as minimal as possible so I can easily restore it if something similar happens.
I don&amp;rsquo;t care so much about distros and I have not had any problems with Mint till this happened. But it is so poor design to overwrite .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>xinitrc</title>
      <link>///home/bud/pub/www/dots/xinitrc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 17:17:15 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>///home/bud/pub/www/dots/xinitrc/</guid>
      <description>This is part of my anti-DM suite. The stuff I want to happen just before i3 loads up, goes here. Having urxvt in daemon mode is really nice. And I use xsetroot and a solid &amp;ldquo;greyed&amp;rdquo; color from Xresources instead of a wallpaper. I have written a little piece about the strange keyboard layout Seba. There is also a short text on why i use sxhkd.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>