<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Guide on Mr Beaner - Put Coffee in your rice!</title>
    <link>https://budrich.github.io/tags/guide/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Guide on Mr Beaner - Put Coffee in your rice!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 19:13:40 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://budrich.github.io/tags/guide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>fresh_start</title>
      <link>https://budrich.github.io/blog/fresh_start/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 19:13:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://budrich.github.io/blog/fresh_start/</guid>
      <description>First thins to do on a fresh install These are the steps I take to setup my work environment on a fresh install of Peppermint OS 8. Most of the steps are valid on other GNU/Linux distributions, but I don&amp;rsquo;t recommend anyone to blindly follow and install everything.
Before doing anything else i start syncing Dropbox. I start with this step because it can take up to 45 minutes, so while Dropbox is syncing there is time to install and setup other programs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>install_i3</title>
      <link>https://budrich.github.io/blog/install_i3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 17:17:39 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://budrich.github.io/blog/install_i3/</guid>
      <description>You can probably install i3 directly from your distributions package manager. But If you want to be sure to get the latest version or a fork you need to download and compile the source code.
i3-gaps i3-gaps is a fork of i3 developed by Airblader who happens to be one of the main developers on vanilla/normal i3. i3-gaps has some features that is not 100% in sync with the design philosophy of normal i3, that&amp;rsquo;s why it is a fork.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>font_rendering</title>
      <link>https://budrich.github.io/blog/font_rendering/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 17:15:34 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://budrich.github.io/blog/font_rendering/</guid>
      <description>It is easy to get used to bad font rendering. But there are some simple steps one can take to get great looking fonts on *GNU/*Linux.
Below is a summary of an article on binarytides, with some spice.
download the following fonts from
http://www.google.com/fonts/
 Droid Sans Droid Sans Mono Droid Serif Noto Sans Noto Serif Open Sans  Unzip &amp;lsquo;em and place them in ~/.fonts Download and place this .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>